<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>home on nhclassen</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in home on nhclassen</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 17:22:36 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nathanclassen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Six</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 17:22:36 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/6/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;We Bene Gesserit sift people to find the humans.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&amp;ndash; The Reverend Mother Gaius Helen Mohiam, &lt;em>Dune&lt;/em>, Frank Herbert&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>five</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 11:09:24 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/5/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>[Gaius Mucious to Porsina after a failed assassination attempt].. &amp;lsquo;when Fortune wore so menacing an aspect, yet as one more to be feared than fearing, &amp;ldquo;I am a Roman citizen,” he cried; “men call me Gaius Mucius. I am your enemy, and as an enemy I would have slain you; I can die as resolutely as I could kill: both to do and to endure valiantly is the Roman way. Nor am I the only one to carry this resolution against you: behind me is a long line of men who are seeking the same honour. Gird yourself therefore, if you think it worth your while, for a struggle in which you must fight for your life from hour to hour with an armed foe always at your door. Such is the war we, the Roman youths, declare on you. Fear no serried ranks, no battle; it will be between yourself alone and a single enemy at a time.” The king, at once hot with resentment and aghast at his danger, angrily ordered the prisoner to be flung into the flames unless he should at once divulge the plot with which he so obscurely threatened him. Whereupon Mucius, exclaiming, “Look, that you may see how cheap they hold their bodies whose eyes are fixed upon renown!” thrust his hand into the fire that was kindled for the sacrifice.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>quick shell script</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/posts/quickshellscript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 17:34:59 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/posts/quickshellscript/</guid><description>&lt;p>Though I am sure most IDEs come packaged with a command to open a desired file or directory within the IDE, I find that creating a quick script to accomplish this task is less taxing than searching for the native IDE command.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After all, one can already specify which applicaiton to use for opening a file via &lt;code>open&lt;/code>, by passing in the &lt;code>-a&lt;/code> option. So writing the tool in question can really be accomplished in a matter of seconds (depending on how quickly one can type I suppose), and then all that&amp;rsquo;s left is to set it up for use anywhere on ones machine.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>amazing creature</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/posts/bug/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 14:19:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/posts/bug/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://nathanclassen.github.io/images/D2289985-4706-488B-AFDD-3322189EBF77.jpeg" alt="leaf bug">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>simply incredible&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Four</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 10:39:51 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/4/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;Would it not be better to live in peace at home, than to stray up and down the world in search of superfine bread without considering that many a one who goes out for wool, comes home quite shorn.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;My dear neice, replied Don Quixote, you are altogether out of your reckoning. Before I be shorn, I will pull and pluck off the beards of all those who pretend to touch a single hair of my mustache.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Two</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 17:22:40 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/2/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>If you desire to be an eccentric and a thinker, a 3/4 turn headshot&amp;ndash;both hands front and center frozen in a grasping gesture&amp;ndash;is of the utmost importance.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>One</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 17:22:36 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/snippets/1/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The more I love humanity in general the less I love man in particular.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&amp;ndash; The Brothers Karamazov, Fyodor Dostoevsky&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>about</title><link>http://nathanclassen.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 17:17:31 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://nathanclassen.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>My name is Nathan Classen.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am a husband, father, autodidact and software engineer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is my personal site wherein I write, collect interesting things and so on.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="in-my-toolbox">in my toolbox&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Golang, Java, Javascript, Ruby&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Hugo, React/Native&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://serverless.com">Serverless&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Docker&lt;/li>
&lt;li>AWS: Lambda, Dynamo, S3, ECS, ECR, API Gateway&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>